there's nothing people like more than
being scared well yeah
oh my God that's why when October swings
around haunted houses are big business
Bruce Stanton is the owner of Reign of
Terror an annual haunted house in
Thousand Oaks California we have a
perfect environment to set you up to be
scared but after taking a walk through
of the supposedly scary mansion I came
out less than impressed hi so I talked
to Bruce one-on-one about an idea I had
to help his business this
just made them for you what is the best
press a haunted house can get that it's
so scary someone peed their pants no
p is one thing I want your haunted house
to be so scary that someone sues you for
being too scary
I don't know that we want people to sue
us if the reign of terror was sued for
being too scary that news would attract
Thrill Seekers from around the world the
plan get customers to sue by making them
think that they're really going to die
no because I think that would be going
too far well your current approach
could get pressed too yes by being the
world's least scary haunted house I
don't think that's the approach we want
well that's the approach it seems like
you're currently taking no we are a
scary reign of terror where go
to relax oh okay or reign of terror
you're probably gonna die you mean in
the haunted house we paint a picture
that their death is
imminent yes okay to scare people enough
that they would sue I explained to Bruce
that we needed to convince customers
they somehow contracted a disease
they're likely to die from Bruce
reluctantly agreed to let me try it out
for a day and after a week of
preparation my actors were ready it was
time for people to enter the world's
scariest haunted house well thanks for
coming to the reign of terror I'll be
excited you excited yeah man I have to
warn you before you go in this haunted
house is extremely scary I like the
sound of that are you sure yeah all
right welcome to the reign of terror
[Music]
sorry one sec wahoo
who her sorry can you come with me for a
sec sorry guys
were you guys scared in there yeah
so sorry did she touch you by any chance
or was there uh
um I think she probably touched my neck
[Music]
usually wear my glasses this time I
didn't and I overshot the grab and I was
supposed to not touch it sorry just
sorry guys waiting here one second sorry
okay what is it called it's called Klein
disease
so so what's the problem she has a
autoimmune thing she worried when she
touched you she transmitted something to
you so don't get freaked out or anything
but I called an ambulance paramax just
come and make sure to look at you it's
just precautionary so just hold tight
thank you so much no problem I hope you
had a good time
sorry about this I did
I didn't think and like twice about her
touching me really because I thought it
was an accident but I know she had like
some kind of
disorder or something so why would they
even let her work here though okay
it makes no sense
doesn't love me I don't know the
Americans with Disabilities Act
it's crazy hey guys hey are we going uh
just in here do you have any Cuts yeah I
don't think so I don't look back there
alive do not okay it was like on this
side I mean we should definitely get her
checked out if that's checked out in
what way like at a hospital with a
doctor for sure for clients yeah
to my knowledge is a disease that's
pretty serious basically if you've got a
cut and you're touched and you have any
sort of open wound or anything that you
know touch an orifice your eye your
mouth or anything that's open or
anything like that you can get yeah it
can be contracted so is this like AIDS
is it like well it's easier immune
deficiency disease so you're talking
about you know a step below age
it's no joke
okay yeah we're gonna go to the east
entrance they want us to go that way
instead of the other side
okay what's that name I've never gone to
the east entrance so usually we just go
straight into the ambulance Bay so I
have no idea
how are we doing
I don't know how should we be doing at
this time it's a precautionary measure
that's all it is it's the first stage
we're gonna have you checked out right
here okay are you a doctor are you a
doctor I am a doctor yes I need her to
come outside with me and we're gonna
move on to another stage where there's
more doctors why are you in this suit is
it serious for my okay yes sir it is
serious please no what is going on
if he's wearing this we
she's not going nowhere till you explain
man what's going on man yeah what's
going on yeah it's not going nowhere
look she's touching me right outside
let's walk right outside okay this is
one explanation that's all I'm asking
for
[Music]
hope you guys enjoyed the haunted house
this right here is a lawyer hello Peter
Peter Peter Mark Mo and you are Amira
Mira so um if you found the haunted
house too scary and you want to press
any legal action against the haunted
house uh he can talk to you and see if
you have a case under the law you have
claims for what we call intentional
infliction of emotional distress or even
negligent infliction of emotional
distress I don't want to create problems
that don't exist but if you have those
concerns feel free to call me but you
don't have to it's only if you're
comfortable about it after running
several more customers through my
version of The Haunted House hey Mom
it's Jordan
um actually I have to go to the hospital
there was somebody with a disease no I'm
not trying to create a lawsuit here I
just you have certain rights under
California alone I paid Bruce a visit to
follow up what did you think well I
think it's completely impractical for a
haunted house but people were scared
yeah I don't know I couldn't tell we had
a lawyer there at the exit that thinks
you know some people might have a case
Peter do you want to hello in hi this is
Bruce
nice to meet you so some of these people
have a case right well some of them were
little apprehensive and I'm not trying
to get you in a lot of trouble but you
want to sue do I want I want to sue for
legitimate claims absolutely and this is
a legitimate claim well it could be and
uh we'll see all right all right thanks
so much all right well I'm glad I you
know can could have helped and done this
for you and I took a good haunted house
and
not made any better
well I'm trying to get you pressed okay
in the end the scariest thing about the
haunted house was Bruce's terrible
manners but when someone's rude to you
you can't take it personally you just
have to keep going
Sue Stanford is one of over 6 000
licensed realtors in LA County and in an
oversaturated Market it can be hard to
stand out from the crowd we're
continually trying to outdo the other
horse person you know trying to get
business so I paid her a visit to help
her become one of the most sought after
realtors in the city so I always like to
begin with some small talk to break the
ice and make the other person
comfortable okay
um have you ever posed for a painting
before
no not actually not for anything like
that you'd make a good model you're very
beautiful well bless your heart thank
you so much for saying that you're
welcome
so is that enough small talk to make you
comfortable
yeah I guess so
um my mission was to make sue one of
LA's top realtors the plan have her
specialize in a currently unrepresented
group of homebuyer the 50 of people who
believe in ghosts
ghosts when you show a house you know
half the people that come through are
thinking is there a ghost in here okay
so it surprised me that I've never seen
a realtor that can guarantee that all
the homes they sell are entirely
ghost-free
true yeah so what I'm suggesting is a
complete rebranding of you as the ghost
realtor
really a wild idea Sue wasn't fully
seeing my vision yet so to help sell a
tour I mocked up some new branding and
prepared a special surprise to get her
excited ready uh-huh all right open your
eyes look
oh my gosh
that's amazing pretty great huh that's
me
my homes are 100 ghost and Demon free oh
my goodness I could tell Sue was
thrilled with her new image but to fully
Rebrand as the ghost realtor she'd need
to work with a professional psychic
medium who could verify whether her
homes were truly ghost-free so I found a
local psychic online
and arranged for he and Sue to meet at
one of her listings my mother was
considered Queen of the psychics by Dr
Hans Holzer he's written 145 books wow
and my daughter just found her first
missing child in New York
okay so just to be clear if there's a
ghost in this house you'll be able to
tell that's correct with Ron's guarantee
I introduced him to sue my great
pleasure and then we followed as he led
us through the house inspecting each
room for the presence of any ghosts
definitely a change of energy you feel
that correct definitely I feel like
Jill's coming down my spine right is it
a ghost no things were off to a great
start as Ron believed the first house
was completely ghost-free I'm not
feeling as many entities in this house
well that's good that's good yes I can
sell the house yeah but when we visited
another one of Sue's listings Ron felt a
presence immediately I'm here he's
screaming and arguing throughout the
house
screaming and arguing yeah this is no
good the bathroom
this whole house something's wrong
wow Ron sensed Evil all around us
something went on back there but it
wasn't until we went into the bedroom
that he felt the true presence of the
ghost do you feel like there's ghosts
around her yeah
oh is that right I feel there are
Anthony's in this house I see there's no
question about it well that sucks for
you
yeah yeah what is his activity in the
house
it's like evil it's like you know what
an incubus is
a ghost that'll have sex with someone
until they die ah wow that's like what I
experienced when I was in Switzerland
something a bad Spirit or a bad entity
this is a room that is generating from
what happened in Switzerland when I was
being choked
in Switzerland yes wow oh yes there's
been many things that has happened in my
life that's why it's interesting to meet
you Sue's bombshell about the
Switzerland ghost made me feel an
urgency to get rid of this entity right
away the only question was how it could
always be cleaned Ron suggested an
exorcism so the next morning I found an
exorcist from Fresno named Brother
Carlos
you have to come out in the name of
Jesus Christ there was and booked him to
do an exorcism in the master bedroom for
the following week it was finally the
night of the exorcism and after Brother
Carlos our Exorcist arrived Sue and I
led him upstairs to the bedroom where
the entity was detected so what I'm
gonna do I'm gonna anoint this this
place okay and I'm going to commend
these spirits to leave in the mighty
name of the Lord Jesus Christ come out
the spirits making people believe you
are Spears of dead humans huh Liars
liars and deceivers get out get out of
here and don't ever ever come back after
getting rid of the spirit Brother Carlos
insisted that he had to cleanse us as
well as demons can sometimes attach
themselves to humans and manifest as
physical ailments do you have any health
issues are you constantly getting sick
do you have migraine headache hitting
you all the time I do have one thing but
it's kind of
uh private personal all right it's a
hemorrhoids
yeah that's the money oh yeah okay so
how do you say it again I don't say this
name very often Amorite
oh hemorrhoids hammers yeah I don't say
this name very often oh I see so let me
go ahead and address this thing right
now okay in the name of the Lord Jesus
Christ I command Demons of hemorrhoids I
am casting you out there with spirits in
the name of their lord Jesus Christ
hemoroid demons
come out
how's it going wow you look different I
do
you look like something just happened
definitely wow if Sue noticed to change
that quickly I wanted to be sure to
leave no stone unturned I can't help
with the penis size
do you see yeah okay if it's demonic
yeah I can cast out the edema from there
I don't have to say for the thing to you
know
increase in size or to me whatever okay
in the name of the Lord Jesus Christ I
command all of you demons if there's a
demon there
um you know affecting this man's
penis male organs
making uh is smaller whatever if there's
any edema there lodged in his penis
right now come out in the name of Jesus
Christ come out
you might be free from this thing
already really oh yeah after Brother
Carlos addressed my personal demons I
have an extremely bad back problem if
that can be oh yeah he offered to help
Sue by removing the demons causing her
back pain and as I am addressing these
demons right now I'm going to be more
aggressive okay because I know you have
signs of someone that have Demons Inside
okay so okay just make eye contact with
me right now okay
in the name of the Lord Jesus Christ I
command any evil spirit that the Lord
Jesus Christ has identified to face
Divine judgment for violating the soul
in the name of the Lord Jesus Christ I
command you now to get out of this woman
right now with your spirits I commit
enough to get out demons look in my eyes
look in my eyes you've been messing up
with her back huh right there I'm
commanding you to come out
I am commanding you to come out
chest come out come out come out your
spirits come out there with Spirits
Demas messing up with the vertebrates of
the neck come out in the name of Jesus
Christ come out I want all Demas out of
our spine get out get out get out get
out get out in the name of Jesus Christ
get out in the name of Jesus Christ get
out come out come out come out come out
in the name of Yeshua come out in the
name of Yeshua come out get out look in
my eyes you have to go now you have to
go I'm casting you out you have to go
you have to go leave now leave now leave
now okay please please stop it leave
stop leave go now and don't ever come
back take a deep breath three times
please
you didn't hurt her or anything right no
okay
because she looks like she's almost dead
are you okay yeah Sue actually I'm fine
I think I'm just feeling a little relief
now it's amazing
ah
foreign
[Music]